As the seasons
change, shouldn't
our health care also change?
The new
health insurance plan introduced by ICICI Bank, Elevate,
has brought about such a change. Let's take a look at its
important features. The
first benefit is Infinite
[Music] Reset.
What will we do if our policy amount is exhausted due to a claim? There is no
need to worry about the Elevate plan.
Your coverage amount will be automatically
restored after each claim. No matter how many times you
claim, the coverage will remain intact. The
second is Infinite Claim. This is a
feature that provides unlimited coverage if any claim requires more than your limit during the policy period.
This is a great relief when it comes to high medical expenses
.  The third
benefit is the Infinite Super Loyalty
Bonus.
Your Sum Assured [Music]
will increase by a certain percentage each year, whether you claim or not.  In regular
plans, the
bonus is often lower due to more work than claims.  But the
reality is that that won't happen here.  Fourth, Jump Start Benefit.
People with diseases like diabetes, BP, etc. usually need a
waiting period of three to four years,
but
through this feature in the Elevate plan [Music], we can get coverage for
such diseases after just 30 days.
Similarly, cashless treatment.
We can get the facility of cashless benefit in more than ten thousand hospitals across India.
Room rent, even if a single private AC room facility is available, we can take a suite room.
In modern
[Music], we
provide coverage for advanced treatments including robotic surgery.
Pre and post hospitalization.
We can get expenses up to 90 days before hospital admission and up to 180 days after discharge.
In short,
Elevate is an AI-powered plan that can make changes according to your health needs. For more information, visit the
ICICI Bank website.  While
visiting, please call
the number shown below [Music] and we will
give you more details.
Thank you.